A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Speech Files, RG 5 FA434
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Speech Files, 1941-2004; 5; 38 document box(es)
  - 2002
    - Rockefeller Family Christmas Luncheon: "Creating two Preeminent Institutions: The Legacy of Bessie Dashiell", 2002 December 15 (Box 38, Folder 598)
      Each adult was given a copy of "Creating Two Preeminent Institutions - The Legacy of Bessie Dashiell."
  - 2003
    - Acceptance of the William Mott Award, National Park Conservation Association, 2003 April 9 (Box 38, Folder 599)
      Henry Diamond responded on behalf of Laurance Rockefeller to the presentation of the Award.
    - British Virgin Islands' Belonger Ceremony Honoring Laurance Rockefeller, 2003 September 26 (Box 38, Folder 600)
  - 2004
    - Dedication of "Cherubim" Window, Union Church, Pocantico Hills: In memory of Mary French Rockefeller and in honor of Laurance S. Rockefeller, 2004 May 2 (Box 38, Folder 601)
      Window in memory of Mary French Rockefeller and in honor of Laurance S. Rockefeller. Ceremonies included thoughts by Laurance Rockefeller.
    - Dedication of "Cherubim" Window, Union Church, Pocantico Hills: In memory of Mary French Rockefeller and in honor of Laurance S. Rockefeller, 2004 May 2 (Box 38, Folder 601A)